hotnewdeal.com 2017-05-28

# Privacy Policy

HotNewDeal, LLC (herein after “HotNewDeal”) values its users on the HotNewDeal.com web site, mobile site and apps (“Properties”) and the services offered on our Properties (we will refer to the Properties and all other services collectively as the “Services”). HotNewDeal has implemented this Privacy Policy to inform users of the information that HotNewDeal collects from you and what HotNewDeal does with it after it is collected. By using the Services, you are agreeing to the practices described in this policy.

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact HotNewDeal at: privacy@HotNewDeal.com.

**Does HotNewDeal.com Ever Make Changes to its Privacy Policy?**

HotNewDeal may make changes to the Privacy Policy from time to time. HotNewDeal will notify you of any changes by sending you an email, Private Message, or posting a notice on our Web site or other Properties. In such case, you should review the new Privacy Policy carefully to make sure you understand HotNewDeal new privacy practices.  If you use the Services after we provide notice of a change, you are necessarily agreeing to the changed terms.

**What Types of Information Does HotNewDeal.com Collect From Me?**

HotNewDeal will collect the personal information you provide when you register, take a survey, sign up for notifications, register for a sweepstakes or giveaway, email us or otherwise send us your information. This information may include your name, email address and other information that can be used to identify you. You can use some of the Services without providing any personal information but some features may not be available.

Each time you use the Services, HotNewDeal also collects other, non-personal information from you, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous web site you visited, your ISP, operating system, and your IP Address. If you access the Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device or other transactional information for that device. If you receive email from us, we will track related information such as if an email is opened and whether you click on an ad or offer in the email. In addition, like the operators of most web sites, HotNewDeal uses analytic and reporting technologies to record information such as Internet domain and host names, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser software and operating system types, clickstream patterns, and the dates and times that the Properties and the other Services are accessed.

If you log in via a third party service like Facebook or Google, we will access the information described in the request for authorization. You should review your privacy settings with these third party services to be sure you are only sharing information you wish to share.

HotNewDeal.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com, amazonsupply.com, or myhabit.com

**What About Cookies?**

In addition, HotNewDeal uses “cookies,” a small data string our server writes to your computer, and other tracking technology to help us manage and track your interaction with the Services. These technologies collect non-personally identifiable information to improve the Services, including to keep count of return visits to the Properties or our advertisers’ or partners’ websites, collect and report on aggregate statistical information, save your password and login information, and display advertising or content based on your interests. HotNewDeal may also collect other data such as search criteria and results, date, time, connection speed and IP addresses. Third parties whose products or services are accessible or advertised via the Services may also use cookies, and we advise you to check their privacy policies for information about their cookies and other privacy practices.

Using Cookies, HotNewDeal.com may collect, use, store, and disclose data collected from visitors, including, where applicable, that third parties (including Google,Amazon and other advertisers) may serve content and advertisements, collect information directly from the website users, and place or recognize cookies on user browsers. 

**Do Third Parties Gather My Information?**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Properties. These companies may use non-personal information (i.e., not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to the Properties and other online properties (e.g., Web sites, mobile sites and apps) in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit <http://www.comworkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. We may also permit third parties to gather non-personal information about our users (e.g., information related to online behavior associated with a particular computer) and to use and share that information with other companies to help them provide relevant advertising on and off our Properties.

In addition, like millions of other websites, we use analytics services provided by third parties such as Google and Flurry. These companies use cookies and other tracking mechanisms to gather data about how users use our Properties. This information will be transmitted to and stored by our analytics providers, who will use this information for purposes such as evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to activity on our Properties and internet usage. These providers may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on their behalf.

We also use Google Analytics for Display Advertising (e.g., Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.)   Google Analytics for Display Advertising allows Google to collect data from DoubleClick cookies in addition to data collected through the standard Google Analytics implementation.  Specifically:

a)    We will use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online.

b)    Third party vendors, including Google, will show our ads on sites across the Internet.

c)    We, along with third-party vendors, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the Double Click cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website.

d)    We, along with third-party vendors, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the Double Click cookie) together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits of our site.

e)    We may use data from Google’s Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender and interests) with Google Analytics to improve the ads you see online, and to give you meaningful choices over how that information is used. Google offers you several ways to control the information that’s gathered through interest-based advertising.

You may opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads at [www.google.com/ads/preferences](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences).

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser and opt out of certain other forms of tracking.   If you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of our Properties.

By using our Services, you consent to the processing of data about you by our third parties analytics provisions as described above. To opt out of Google Analytics, please visit <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>.

**How Does HotNewDeal Use My Information?**

HotNewDeal uses the information collected from users for the following purposes:

To customize and personalize the advertising and the content you see.

To fulfill your requests for certain Services.

To send you information that you agreed to receive about topics that we think will be of interest to you.

To alert you to the latest developments and features on our Services.

**When Will HotNewDeal Disclose My Information to Third Parties?**

We may make your personally identifiable information available to other companies or people. For example:

Information you disclose when you participate in community and social networking features will be shared with other users. HotNewDeal is not responsible for the information you disclose in public forums and we strongly recommend that you only disclose your personal information to other users that you know to be trustworthy.

We may share information you allow us to share when you register with us, or through a subsequent affirmative election.

We may share information with third party vendors who are providing services on our behalf, such as data processing and hosting.

User information may be shared in connection with an actual or potential merger, sale or acquisition of HotNewDeal, or in the event of a sale or transfer of all or some of our assets.

We may share your information in order to (i) protect or defend our legal rights or property or the rights/property of our other users, business partners, employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of our users or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for other risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process.

We also may use and share non-personally identifiable information, such as general demographic or location information, or information about the computer or device from which you access the Service. Additionally, we may de-identify personally identifiable information and share it in a de-identified or aggregated form with third parties, advertisers and/or business partners for our own business purposes and for third party marketing and other purposes. The use and disclosure of such information is not subject to any restrictions under this Privacy Policy.

**Security**

HotNewDeal uses commercially reasonable measures to protect your personal information. However, despite these measures, no method of online transmission or storage is 100% secure.

**Does This Privacy Policy Apply When I Access Third Party Sites?**

You may be able to access third-party web sites, mobile sites and/or apps directly from links on the Properties. This Privacy Policy does not apply when you access such properties. HotNewDeal cannot control how third parties may use your information so you should carefully review the privacy policy of any third-party properties you visit before using it or disclosing your any information to its provider.

**Consent to Processing**

HotNewDeal collects, processes and stores information in the United States. By using the Services outside of the United States, you consent to the transfer of your personal information to, and the collection and processing of such personal information in the United States and other countries or territories. The laws on personal information in the United States may vary and be less stringent than laws of your state or country.

**What About Children’s Privacy?**

**Under Thirteen**

The HotNewDeal Services are only for users ages 13 and older. Accordingly, HotNewDeal will not knowingly collect any information from a child under the age of 13.

**Thirteen to Seventeen**

HotNewDeal insists that prospective users between the ages of 13 and 17 using the Services should be under their parents’ or legal guardian’s supervision while using the Services.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, users who are California residents may request and receive once a year, free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we disclosed personal information (if any) for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the categories of personal information disclosed to those third parties. If you wish to make such a request, you may send an email to privacy@HotNewDeal.com

**What About Cookies?**

A cookie is a message that is sent to your computer from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. With respect to cookies: HotNewDeal uses cookies. Cookies help us save your preferences and allow you to login to participate in the community forums. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by HotNewDeal.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Last updated September 3, 2014**
